export const verbPracticeDataFrancais = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Je", answer: "suis" },
    { prompt: "Tu", answer: "es" },
    { prompt: "Il", answer: "est" },
    { prompt: "Elle", answer: "est" },
    { prompt: "Ce", answer: "est" },
    { prompt: "suis", answer: "je" },
    { prompt: "es", answer: "tu" },
    { prompt: "est", answer: "il/elle/ce" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "J", answer: "ai" },
    { prompt: "Tu", answer: "as" },
    { prompt: "Il", answer: "a" },
    { prompt: "Elle", answer: "a" },
    { prompt: "Ce", answer: "a" },
    { prompt: "ai", answer: "je" },
    { prompt: "as", answer: "tu" },
    { prompt: "a", answer: "il/elle/ce" }
  ]
};
